Name: Beakal Lemeneh
Net ID: 31390484
Project Number: 03

1a)

I did not collaborate with anyone in this assignment.


1b)

I did not use any outside source to code this project.


1c)

I have implemented all the functions described on the project manual. I think this will qualify me to get the maximum extra credit possible. 

I have made the repl very user friendly. The program prompts the user to enter a function that the user chooses, and takes the arguments as an input form from the user.


